camyoo.com 2013-08-05

# CamYoo

Camyoo LLC (" Camyoo LLC," "us" or "we"), has created this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy and have designed our website with this in mind. Camyoo LLC is fully committed to 100% permission-based marketing. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: 1) access or use our website located at www.camyoo.com (the "Website"); 2) agree to receive e-mail from us; 3) obtain, or attempt to obtain, services (the "Service") from Camyoo LLC properties at this Website or at a website belonging to an affiliate of Camyoo LLC; and/or 4) register for one of our sweepstakes contests (the "Sweepstakes"). 

This Privacy Policy will address the following: 

1\. What information this Website gathers/tracks about you.   
2\. What this Website does with the information it gathers/tracks.   
3\. With whom this Website shares the information it gathers/tracks.   
4\. This Website's opt-out policy.   
5\. This Website's policy on correcting and updating personally identifiable information.   
6\. This Website's policy on deactivating your name from our database. 

**Information Collected Online Registration/Application**  
We provide an online application and/or information request forms to process your request for Service. Understand that the information that you submit is voluntary, but required if you request Services and/or enter one of our Sweepstakes, whether or not you enter into a formal application with Camyoo LLC. Upon registration, users may be required to provide personal information including, but not limited to, the following: 

1\. Name   
2\. Gender   
3\. E-mail address   
4\. Street Address   
5\. Zip Code   
6\. Daytime Telephone Number and Nighttime Telephone Number or Cellular Telephone Number   
7\. Credit Card Information   
8\. Social Security Number   
9\. Birth Date   
10\. Reference Information   
11\. Driver's License Number   
12\. Answers to various questions, including providing authorization to access your credit report. 

The aforementioned registration/application information, together with information regarding your transactions with Camyoo LLC is referred to, collectively, herein as "Personal Information." 

**IP Addresses**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our 

Website. Your IP address is used to gather broad and specific demographic information as well as for validation purposes. 

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time that you visit our Website (if you choose), and for other purposes. 

**Web Site Tracking Software**  
Web servers, or those of third-party vendors, utilize certain tracking software to capture your domain name address (the address of your Internet service provider) for purposes of tracking Website statistics. Note that we only collect information about you when you voluntarily provide that information through an application or registration, by visiting the Website request form, or some other Website activity we may provide from time to time. The capture of your domain name is a common practice among websites for measuring the number of hits, pages visited, and length of user session. We use this information to measure the effectiveness of the Website offerings in order to service you better. 

**Sharing of Information  
Camyoo LLC respects your privacy. We will never share your personal information with a third party, unless required by law. You agree that by submitting your e-mail address at the Website you may receive e-mail marketing and/or 3rd party offers from Camyoo LLC. With respect to the ATSR, and notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, Camyoo LLC retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the terms of the ATSR.**

Camyoo LLC reserves the right to release current or past user information and Personal Information: a) in the event that we believe that the Website and/or the Service is being or has been used in violation of the Website Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; or b) if the information is subpoenaed. Moreover, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when Camyoo LLC, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time. 

**Other Websites**  
This Website may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites. Camyoo LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of their third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Camyoo LLC has no responsibility or liability relating to them. 

**Security**  
All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. When our registration/application process asks users to enter sensitive information (such as bank account information, Social Security Number, etc), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a loan specialist or a customer service representative) are granted access to Personal Information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all Camyoo LLC user information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your Personal Information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures. 

**Minors**  
Visitors under 18 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at our Website and are not allowed to participate in the Sweepstakes offered by Camyoo LLC. Camyoo LLC does not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under 18 years of age. Camyoo LLC encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. 

**Opt-Out/Unsubscribe**  
To stop receiving future communications from Camyoo LLC, please [Click Here](http://www.camyoo.com/unsubscribe.html). Camyoo LLC uses Personal Information to provide promotional offers by e-mail to individuals. Camyoo LLC may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If e-mail recipients wish to end their e-mail subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all Camyoo LLC e-mail lists, please [Click Here](http://www.camyoo.com/unsubscribe.html). 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**  
Camyoo LLC reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice at the Website explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use Personal Information changes, Camyoo LLC will notify its users by posting the changes on the Website and sending out an e-mail notification to its customers notifying them of the changes, and providing them with the opportunity to opt-out of the provisions relating to the transfer of their Personal Information. Other than where the user opts-out, and other than where affirmative consent is required for California residents and Vermont residents, the user's continued use of the Camyoo LLC service and/or continued receipt of Camyoo LLC e-mails constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by the user of the modified Privacy Policy. 

**Contacting the Website**  
Our "About Us" page contains information that allows you to contact us directly with any questions or comments that you may have. We listen to or read every message sent in and endeavor to reply promptly to each one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of Camyoo LLC, please feel free to contact us at [support@camyoo.com](mailto:support@camyoo.com)
